A Guide to the Foundation Center of New York records FA023
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Program and Project Files, 1924-1999; 2
  - Programs, 1924-1998; 1
    - Sponsors, 1972-1985; F
      - Summary of Fund-Raising Results 1974, 1976-1977 (Reel 143, Frame 72)
      - Support Granted or Pledged for 1977-1978 (Reel 143, Frame 138)
      - Summary of Fund-Raising Results 1977-1978 (Reel 143, Frame 225)
      - Support Granted or Pledged for 1978-1979 (Reel 143, Frame 316)
      - Summary of Fund-Raising Results 1979 (Reel 143, Frame 415)
      - Support Allocated to Cleveland and San Francisco Field OFfices, 1979 (Reel 143, Frame 501)
      - Series 2.1F - Programs and Projects Files - Programs - Sponsors - Attachments, 1977-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 534)
      - The Abelard Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 560)
      - Louis and Anne Abrons Foundation, Inc., 1977-1986 (Reel 143, Frame 584)
      - The Achelis Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 143, Frame 592)
      - Aetna Life and Casualty Foundation, 1978-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 622)
      - The Agricultural Development Council, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 637)
      - The Ahmanson Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 664)
      - AHS Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 702)
      - Akron Community Trust, 1975-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 742)
      - Alcoa Foundation, 1972-1983 (Reel 143, Frame 775)
      - Allied Chemical Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 817)
      - Altman Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 143, Frame 861)
      - Amax Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 874)
      - American Can Company Foundation, 1972-1983 (Reel 143, Frame 899)
      - American Express Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 914)
      - American Standard Foundation, 1978 (Reel 143, Frame 965)
      - AMFAC Inc., 1977-1979 (Reel 143, Frame 968)
      - AMOCO Foundation, Inc., 1972-1985 (Reel 143, Frame 977)
      - John W. Anderson Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 1004)
      - The ARCA Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 1029)
      - The Arcadia Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 1097)
      - Armco Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 143, Frame 1109)
      - J. Aron Charitable Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 143, Frame 1122)
      - The Vincent Astor Foundation, 1972-1978 (Reel 143, Frame 1141)
      - Atkinson Foundation, 1974-1978 (Reel 143, Frame 1168)
      - Atlantic Richfield Foundation, 1972-1985 (Reel 144, Frame 1)
      - The Austin Memorial Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 49)
      - Avon Products Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 67)
      - Mary Reynolds Babcock Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 98)
      - Bank of America Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 167)
      - Bankers Trust Company Fund, 1978 (Reel 144, Frame 186)
      - The Barker Welfare Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 189)
      - The Bass Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 215)
      - Adelaide Breed Bayrd Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 245)
      - Beazley Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 271)
      - Beatrice Companies, Inc., 1975-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 291)
      - The Lowell Berry Foundation, 1976-1979 (Reel 144, Frame 310)
      - Benwood Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 316)
      - Alvin M. Bentley Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 340)
      - The Mary Duke Biddle Foundation, 1972-1985 (Reel 144, Frame 358)
      - Mr. Bingham's Trust for Charity, 1976-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 418)
      - The William Bingham Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 440)
      - The Bodman Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 144, Frame 511)
      - The Boehm Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 559)
      - Booth Ferris Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 590)
      - Borden Foundation, Inc., 1978-1979 (Reel 144, Frame 647)
      - Mary Owen Borden Memorial Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 144, Frame 653)
      - The Bothin Helping Fund, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 664)
      - Otto Bremer Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 688)
      - The Brunswick Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 716)
      - The Bullitt Foundation, Inc., 1976-1979 (Reel 144, Frame 730)
      - Florence V. Burden Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 737)
      - The Burkitt Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 775)
      - The Burroughs Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 793)
      - The Bush Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 827)
      - Patrick and Aimee Butler Family Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 911)
      - The Bydale Foundation, 1974-1985 (Reel 144, Frame 943)
      - Godfrey L. Cabot Family Charitable Trust, 1976-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 971)
      - The Louis Calder Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 991)
      - The Gunard Berry Carlson Memorial Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 1054)
      - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1972-1981 (Reel 144, Frame 1088)
      - Mary Flagler Cary Charitable Trust, 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 1169)
      - Samuel N. and Mary Castle Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 1248)
      - Central Broadcasting System (CBS) Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 144, Frame 1290)
      - Champion International Corporation, 1974-1979 (Reel 144, Frame 1344)
      - Robert Lee and Thomas M. Chastain Charitable Foundation, 1976-1982 (Reel 144, Frame 1355)
      - Chemical Bank, 1978 (Reel 144, Frame 1377)
      - Chevron, United States of America, Inc., 1980 (Reel 144, Frame 1381)
      - The Chicago Community Trust, 1974-1985 (Reel 144, Frame 1386)
      - Clark Foundation, 1977-1985 (Reel 145, Frame 1)
      - Robert Sterling Clark Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 16)
      - The Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1970-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 85)
      - The Cleveland Foundation, 1978-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 174)
      - The Cleveland Electric Illuminating Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 225)
      - The George W. Codrington Charitable Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 244)
      - The Columbus Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 269)
      - The Commonwealth Fund, 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 343)
      - Compton Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 392)
      - David C. Cook Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 414)
      - Charles M. and Anna C. Cooke, Ltd., 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 434)
      - Queene Ferry Coonley Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 461)
      - Cooper Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 490)
      - Adolph Coors Foundation, 1978-1979 (Reel 145, Frame 518)
      - Peter C. Cornell Trust, 1976-1985 (Reel 145, Frame 534)
      - Gardner and Florence Call Cowles Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 563)
      - Bruce L. Crary Foundation, Inc., 1979-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 594)
      - The Mary A. Crocker Trust, 1974-1979 (Reel 145, Frame 606)
      - Crown Zellerbach Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 619)
      - The Dammann Fund, Inc., 1975-1979 (Reel 145, Frame 635)
      - Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 658)
      - Cummins Engine Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 706)
      - The Charles A. Dana Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 763)
      - The Danforth Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 839)
      - Fred Harris Daniels Foundation, Inc., 1975-1985 (Reel 145, Frame 920)
      - The Arthur Vining Davis Foundations, 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 948)
      - Day Companies Foundation, Inc., 1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1006)
      - Dayton Hudson Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 145, Frame 1012)
      - The Ira W. DeCamp Foundation, 1979-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1026)
      - John Deere Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1037)
      - The DeKalb AgResearch Foundation, 1976-1985 (Reel 145, Frame 1065)
      - Deluxe Check Printers Foundation, 1978-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1085)
      - Division Fund/The Distribution Fund, 1976-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1096)
      - Cleveland H. Dodge Foundation, Inc., 1972-1985 (Reel 145, Frame 1122)
      - Geraldine R. Dodge Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1175)
      - Carrie Estelle Doheny Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 145, Frame 1199)
      - The Henry L. and Grace Doherty Charitable Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1240)
      - Dolfinger-McMahon Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1286)
      - The Gaylord Donnelley Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1323)
      - Dr. Scholl Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1354)
      - The Camille & Henry Dreyfus Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1405)
      - The Max & Victoria Dreyfus Foundation, Inc., 1977-1980 (Reel 145, Frame 1465)
      - The Duke Endowment, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1)
      - Dyer-Ives Foundation, 1976-1985 (Reel 146, Frame 29)
      - The Dyson Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 48)
      - Earhart Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 63)
      - The East Bay Community Foundation, 1976-1985 (Reel 146, Frame 85)
      - The East Ohio Gas Company, 1976-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 100)
      - The Eaton Charitable Fund, 1976-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 116)
      - Lettie Pate Evans Foundation, Inc., 1974-1985 (Reel 146, Frame 133)
      - Exxon Corporation, 1973 (Reel 146, Frame 173)
      - Exxon Education Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 179)
      - Maurice Falk Medical Fund, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 245)
      - Isadore and Sunny Familian Family Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 315)
      - Samuel S. Fels Fund, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 332)
      - Field Enterprises Charitable Corporation, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 377)
      - The Field Foundation, Inc., 1972-1985 (Reel 146, Frame 414)
      - Leland Fikes Foundation, Inc., 1974-1985 (Reel 146, Frame 447)
      - Fireman's Fund American Foundation, 1979-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 468)
      - Fisher Charitable Trust, 1974-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 481)
      - Max C. Fleischmann Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 500)
      - Mortimer Fleishhacker Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 567)
      - The Flinn Foundation, 1979 (Reel 146, Frame 607)
      - The Ford Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 611)
      - The Edward E. Ford Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 773)
      - Foundation for Child Development, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 825)
      - Foundation for Microbiology, 1975-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 873)
      - The Harry K. Fox and Emma R. Fox Charitable Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 901)
      - Parker B. Francis Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 934)
      - Frear Eleemonsynary Trust, 1975-1985 (Reel 146, Frame 957)
      - The Fund for New Jersey, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 994)
      - Fund for The City of New York, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1040)
      - The Furth Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1091)
      - Frank E. Gannett Newspaper Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1109)
      - Garvey Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1181)
      - Gates Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1216)
      - Gebbie Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 146, Frame 1278)
      - Eva Gebhard-Gourgaud Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1334)
      - The General Electric Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 146, Frame 1369)
      - The General Foods Fund, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1399)
      - General Mills Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1413)
      - Gerber Baby Foods Fund, 1975-1980 (Reel 146, Frame 1468)
      - Wallace Alexander Gerbode Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1)
      - The German Marshall Fund of the United States, 1975-1979 (Reel 147, Frame 43)
      - Benjamin S. Gerson Family Foundation, 1979-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 81)
      - Getty Oil Company Foundation, 1979 (Reel 147, Frame 98)
      - Josephine Goodyear Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 101)
      - Grace Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 118)
      - Philip L. Graham Fund, 1974-1979 (Reel 147, Frame 165)
      - The Grant Foundation, Inc., 1972-1976 (Reel 147, Frame 178)
      - William T. Grant Foundation, 1977-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 216)
      - The Harry Greenburg Foundation, Inc., 1975-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 274)
      - Susan Greenwal Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 288)
      - The Lucile and Robert H. Gries Charity Fund, 1975-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 308)
      - Grotto Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 337)
      - Ernest A. Grunsfeld Memorial Fund, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 365)
      - The Guinzburg Fund, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 380)
      - Gulf & Western Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 394)
      - The George Gund Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 444)
      - Evelyn and Walter Haas, Jr. Fund, 1980 (Reel 147, Frame 537)
      - Josephine and Peter Haas Fund, 1976-1979 (Reel 147, Frame 543)
      - Paul and Mary Haas Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 547)
      - The Luke B. Hancock Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 577)
      - The Hankins Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 621)
      - The Phil Hardin Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 636)
      - John H. and Wilhelmina D. Harland Charitable Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 652)
      - The Harris Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 664)
      - The William H. and Mattie Wattis Harris Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 685)
      - The John A. Hartford Foundation, 1972-1982 (Reel 147, Frame 706)
      - Charles Hayden Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 147, Frame 775)
      - The Edward W. Hazen Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 821)
      - William Randolph Hearst Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 894)
      - H. J. Heinz Company Foundation, 1976-1982 (Reel 147, Frame 964)
      - Howard Heinz Endowment, 1974-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 973)
      - Mark P. Herschede Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1012)
      - The William & Flora Hewlett Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1038)
      - Hewlett-Packard Foundation, 1979-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1084)
      - The Hillman Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1183)
      - The Hoffmann-La Roche Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1189)
      - The Howard and Bush Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1236)
      - The Lillia Babbitt Hyde Foundation and The John Jay and Eliza Jane Watson Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1264)
      - INA Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1393)
      - Independence Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 147, Frame 1426)
      - The Indianapolis Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 1)
      - International Business Machines (IBM) Corporation, 1978-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 27)
      - International Paper Company Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 46)
      - ITT Corporation (The International Telephone and Telegraph), 1978-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 87)
      - The James Irvine Foundation, 1972-1981 (Reel 148, Frame 104)
      - Ittleson Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 143)
      - The JDR 3rd Fund, Inc., 1972-1984 (Reel 148, Frame 201)
      - The J. M. Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 245)
      - The Ralph and Adolph Jacobs Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 282)
      - Janesville Foundation, Inc., 1975-1979 (Reel 148, Frame 297)
      - Martha Holden Jennings Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 315)
      - The Andrew Jergens Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 354)
      - Jerome Foundation, Inc./Avon Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 394)
      - George Frederick Jewett Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 433)
      - The Johnson Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 476)
      - Christian A. Johnson Endeavor Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 567)
      - Johnson and Johnson Associated Industries Fund, 1975-1983 (Reel 148, Frame 597)
      - The Robert Wood Johnson Foundation, 1972-1986 (Reel 148, Frame 612)
      - The S. S. Johnson Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 999)
      - Daisy Marquis Jones Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 1017)
      - W. Alton Jones Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 148, Frame 1040)
      - The Joyce Foundation, 1976-1981 (Reel 149, Frame 1)
      - Alfred Jurzykowski Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 44)
      - The Henry J. Kaiser Family Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 75)
      - The J. M. Kaplan Fund, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 137)
      - William R. Kenan, Jr. Charitable Trust, 1972-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 169)
      - The Kerr Foundation, Inc., 1976-1979 (Reel 149, Frame 228)
      - Kerr-McGee Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 239)
      - Charles F. Kettering Foundation, 1975-1981 (Reel 149, Frame 265)
      - Kimberly-Clark Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 391)
      - The Kiplinger Foundation, Inc., 1975-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 435)
      - F. M. Kirby Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 468)
      - The Kissinger Family Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 514)
      - Robert J. Kleberg, Jr. and Helen C. Kleberg Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 531)
      - The Esther and Joseph Klingenstein Fund, Inc., 1974-1983 (Reel 149, Frame 549)
      - Knight Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 570)
      - Koret Foundation, 1980 (Reel 149, Frame 631)
      - Samuel H. Kress Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 646)
      - The Kroc Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 713)
      - Kulas Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 750)
      - The Albert Kunstadter Family Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 149, Frame 784)
      - The Laras Fund, 1976-1978 (Reel 149, Frame 800)
      - The Laub Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 810)
      - The Lavanburg-Corner House, 1975-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 827)
      - The Lazar Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 867)
      - The Robert Ingram Leitch and Carrie Scott Leitch Foundation, Inc., 1976-1979 (Reel 149, Frame 880)
      - Leslie Fund, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 901)
      - Lever Brothers Company, 1976-1985 (Reel 149, Frame 922)
      - Levi Strauss Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 149, Frame 947)
      - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1972-1981 (Reel 150, Frame 1)
      - Lincoln Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 190)
      - Albert A. and Bertram N. Linder Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 210)
      - The Joe and Emily Lowe Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 227)
      - Loyola Foundation, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 255)
      - The LTV Corporation, 1978-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 277)
      - The Lubrizol Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 304)
      - The Lukens Steel Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 326)
      - The Lumpkin Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 361)
      - Louis R. Lurie Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 391)
      - Miranda Lux Foundation, 1974-1979 (Reel 150, Frame 431)
      - Lyndhurst Foundation/Memorial Welfare Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 440)
      - The J. E. and L. E. Mabee Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 504)
      - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1979-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 539)
      - Josiah Macy, Jr. Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 580)
      - The John and Mary R. Markle Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 605)
      - The Marsden Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 670)
      - Harriet McDaniel Marshall Trust in Memory of Sanders McDaniel, 1976-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 687)
      - Elizabeth Ring Mather and William Gwinn Mather Fund, 1974-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 708)
      - Richard Mather Fund, 1976-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 728)
      - S. Livingston Mather Charitable Trust, 1960-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 743)
      - The Maytag Company Foundation, Inc., 1978-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 795)
      - James J. McCann Charitable Trust, 1974-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 804)
      - Robert R. McCormack Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 843)
      - McDonald's Corporation, 1978-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 878)
      - McInerny Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 991)
      - McGregor Fund, 1972-1980 (Reel 150, Frame 1021)
      - Foremost-McKesson Foundation, Inc., 1975-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 1)
      - The McKnight Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 21)
      - Meadows Foundation, Inc., 1974-1979 (Reel 151, Frame 50)
      - The Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 63)
      - Richard King Mellon Foundation, 1968-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 149)
      - The Merck Company Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 199)
      - Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner & Smith Foundation, Inc., 1972-1979 (Reel 151, Frame 254)
      - Joyce Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1972-1985 (Reel 151, Frame 272)
      - Mervyn's, 1980 (Reel 151, Frame 322)
      - Metropolitan Life Foundation, 1978-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 327)
      - Eugene and Agnes E. Meyer Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 345)
      - Milbank Memorial Fund, 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 398)
      - The Miller Foundation and Albert L. and Louise B. Miller Foundation, Inc., 1974-1985 (Reel 151, Frame 450)
      - Mobil Oil Corporation, 1972-1979 (Reel 151, Frame 490)
      - Monsanto Fund, 1972-1985 (Reel 151, Frame 507)
      - Morgan Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1972-1985 (Reel 151, Frame 542)
      - Henry and Lucy Moses Fund, Inc., 1975-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 591)
      - M. J. Murdock Charitable Trust/The Millicent Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 622)
      - John P. Murphy Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 663)
      - David and Inez Myers Fund, 1979-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 696)
      - The Needmor Fund, 1975-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 707)
      - The New World Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 735)
      - New York Foundation, 1972-1979 (Reel 151, Frame 760)
      - The New York Community Trust, 1976-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 780)
      - The New York Times Company Foundation, Inc., 1972-1985 (Reel 151, Frame 848)
      - Edward John Noble Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 880)
      - The Samuel Roberts Noble Foundation, Inc., 1974-1979 (Reel 151, Frame 954)
      - Nordson Foundation, 1977-1981 (Reel 151, Frame 967)
      - Northwest Area Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 992)
      - Jessie Smith Noyes Foundation, Inc., 1972-1980 (Reel 151, Frame 1071)
      - The A. Lindsay and Olive B. O'Connor Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 1)
      - John M. Olin Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 54)
      - Spencer T. and Ann W. Olin Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 71)
      - Onan Family Foundation, 1975-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 109)
      - Paccar Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 128)
      - The David and Lucile Packard Foundation, 1972-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 140)
      - The Pew Memorial Trust/The Glenmede Trust Company, 1974-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 179)
      - The Pfizer Foundation, Inc., 1975-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 284)
      - Phillips Petroleum Foundation, Inc., 1976-1979 (Reel 152, Frame 299)
      - The Pillsbury Company Foundation, 1976-1978 (Reel 152, Frame 304)
      - The Pillsbury Foundation, 1974-1985 (Reel 152, Frame 309)
      - The Pinkerton Foundation, 1976-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 327)
      - Pitcairn-Crabbe Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 345)
      - The Piton Foundation, 1979-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 371)
      - The Pittsburgh Foundation, 1974-1985 (Reel 152, Frame 390)
      - Polaroid Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 416)
      - Potlatch Corporation, 1976-1985 (Reel 152, Frame 453)
      - The Powell Family Foundation, 1977-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 465)
      - The Presser Foundation, 1974-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 480)
      - The Louis and Harold Price Foundation, Inc., 1974-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 507)
      - The Prudential Foundation, 1979-1985 (Reel 152, Frame 526)
      - Public Welfare Foundation, Inc., 1974-1985 (Reel 152, Frame 550)
      - Henry A. Rafsky Research Fund, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 594)
      - The Reinberger Foundation, 1977-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 609)
      - Republic Steel Corporation Educational and Charitable Trust, 1972-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 622)
      - Research Corporation, 1972-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 667)
      - R. J. Reynolds Industries, Inc., 1979-1980 (Reel 152, Frame 720)